Welcome to Miami.
欢迎光临迈阿密
While in the airport, please observe Florida and local laws...
根据佛罗里达州的法律 在机场大厅内
...which prohibit smoking in the terminal.
请勿吸烟
Thank you for not smoking.
感谢配合
迈阿密国际机场
哈里斯堡机场
你女婿白天处理干洗生意
Your son-in-law dealt with the dry cleaning franchise during the day.
他每晚都见那女人
He saw that woman every night.
详情在我的报告内 还有那女人的资料
The specifics are in my report, and information about the woman.
我了解这事很不愉快
It's unpleasant, I know.
他不是很谨慎吗？
Discreet, isn't he?
蠢货
What an imbecile!
我尝试警告我女儿
I tried to warn my daughter...
但你能做什么？
...but what can you do?
我担心孩子
I worry about the children.
如果没有别的事 我的账单在信封内
My invoice is in the envelope, if that's all.
好谢谢你威尔斯先生
Yes, Mr. Welles. Thank you.
如果我还有什么可以帮忙 请随时与我联络 参议员
Let me know if I can be of further assistance to you, Senator.
保持联络
I'll be in touch.
有人吗？
Hello?
你回来了
You're home.
我们在这里
We're back here.
一切顺利吗？
How did it go?
还不错吧
I think very well.
很好
Good.
甜心爹地回来了
Daddy's home, sweetie.
你教科书工作如何？
How's the textbook business?
那个联邦剧场的方案 我收到一份一万字的材料
I got 10,000 words on the federal theatre project.
应该只有四千字 但作者拒绝修改
It should be 4,000 and the writer doesn't want to change anything.
所以有点麻烦
So kind of bad.
迈阿密怎样？
How was Miami?
不错只是寂寞
Fine. Lonesome.
就算付我很多钱 我也不要住在那
Couldn't pay me enough to live down there.
那你为什么去？
Then why'd you go?
迈克尔森议员有很多有势力的朋友
Senator Michaelson has powerful friends.
哈啰仙蒂
Hello, Cinderella.
想我吗？我好想你
Did you miss me? I sure missed you.
-她很想你 -这才对
-She missed you. -That's my girl.
她想你我也想你
She missed you. I missed you.
你吸烟？
You been smoking?
吸烟？ 我没有吸烟
Smoking? I'm not smoking.
别这样宝贝
Come on, honey.
你一身的烟味
You reek of it.
艾美我坐在酒吧内 跟踪那男人
Amy, I've been sitting around in bars following this guy.
这就是你给我的见面礼？
Is this the first thing I get?
-你在指责我吗？ -我没有指责你
-You're accusing me? -I'm not accusing you.
我没有吸烟好不好？ 我们以前就讲过了
I'm not smoking, okay? We've been all through that.
我去弄晚餐你肚子饿吗？
I'll make dinner. Are you hungry?
你烧饭？
You're cooking?
我想你
I missed you.
我不喜欢你不在家
I don't like it when you leave.
该我去吗？
Should I go?
我去吧
I'm going to do it.
来吧
Come on.
有什么事仙蒂？
What's all the trouble, Cinderella?
乖乖
There, there.
我爱你
I love you.
宝贝 电话
Honey, phone!
好我在听
Okay, I've got it!
对不起我正在换电话
Sorry, I was just switching phones.
很荣幸认识你 朗先生
It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance, Mr. Longdale.
我有什么能为你效劳？
How can I be of assistance to you?
四点整没问题
Four o'clock would be fine.
我想我知道在那里
I think I know where it is.
威尔斯先生 我是丹尼·朗 我们通过电话
Mr. Welles, Daniel Longdale. We spoke on the phone.
你好
Pleasure.
我是克里斯家族的律师和财产处理人
I'm the Christians' attorney and one of the executors of the estate.
这位是克里斯太太
This is Mrs. Christian.
很荣幸认识你夫人
It's an honour to meet you, ma'am.
威尔斯先生 你有很高的评价
You come highly recommended, Mr. Welles.
我和我在哈里斯堡兰卡士达 以及荷西的合伙人谈过
I've spoken to assoclates of mine in Harrisburg and Lancaster and Hershey.
你认识很多有影响力的人物
You have influential friends.
我很庆幸可以为我崇拜的人提供服务
I've been privileged to provide services for people I admire.
你的谨慎被赞赏
You were praised for your discretion...
还有你能保守秘密
...your strict adherence to confidentiality.
谢谢你夫人
Thank you, ma'am.
你知道我丈夫最近逝世
As you know, my husband passed away recently.
请节哀夫人
My condolences, Mrs. Christian.
他的离开留给我….
His passing has left me...
一些需要解决的事
...with a dilemma.
我会尽力帮忙
I'll do whatever I can to help.
这是我丈夫的私人书房
My husband's inner sanctum.
没有什么人曾经进入这房内
Not many people have been inside this room.
我父亲在匹兹堡钢铁场工作
My father worked the Pittsburgh mill.
我相信是尔稳联合钢铁
Irving United Steel, I believe.
但你拿到宾州大学奖学金
But you attended Penn on an academic scholarship.
没错
That's right.
你同学都念法律和财经 而你选择侦探学
Peers went into law and finance, but you chose surveillance.
我知道那才是将来
I decided it was the future.
你丈夫是个传奇
Your husband is a legend.
请坐
Please.
我们结婚四十五年
We were married 45 years.
四个儿女七个孙子
Four children, seven grandchildren.
但他真正醉心的
But his true passion lay...
是他的工作
...in his work.
但他一直很忠心
But he was always loyal.
我非常地
I loved him...
深爱他
...deeply.
我明白
I understand.
丹尼
Daniel.
只有我丈夫一人知道这保险箱的密码
My husband was the only one with the combination to this safe.
我们请人把它打开
We had to hire somebody to open it.
我避免让任何人
I prevented anyone...
看保险箱内的东西
...from seeing the contents.
我觉得那是我丈夫的私人物品
I felt these were my husband's private things.
我没有…..
I didn't....
我没有察觉….
I didn't realize....
你想告诉我发现什么吗？
Do you want to tell me what you found?
现金股票
Cash, stock certificates.
没有什么不寻常真的除了….
Nothing out of the ordinary, really, except that.
一套短片
It's a film...
好像有个少女被杀
...where a girl appears to be murdered.
我不肯定我明白
I'm not sure I understand.
拍的很真实
It's very realistic.
但每天有多少人在电影或电视上
But how many people seem to be realistically killed...
好像真的被杀害
in movies and on TV every day?
开始时像一套低俗的色情电影
It begins as a relatively sleazy bit of pornography...
但突然变的很暴力和血腥
...and rapidly turns quite violent and bloody.
你所说的叫色情暴力电影
What you're talking about is called a snuff film.
据我所知 色情暴力电影是都市神话
From what I know, snuff films are an urban myth.
性行业的传说根本没有这回事
Sex industry folklore. There's no such thing.
我也这样向克里斯太太解释
That's what I explained to Mrs. Christian.
这可能是一些性虐待的电影
This is probably an SM film of some sort.
模拟强奸模拟暴力
Simulated rape, simulated violence.
令人倒胃口 但都是拍出来的
It's hard to stomach, but there are ways of doing it.
假血浆特别效果
Fake blood, special effects.
请你看完这影片后 告诉我你的意见
Would you look at the film and give us your opinion?
我只希望
All I want...
知道这暴行是假的
...is to know that this atrocity is false.
我要证据
I want the proof.
嗯….
Well...
拍这电影的人拍的非常传神
...whoever made the film was adept at authenticity.
我不是专家 但是我提议让警方去决定
But I'm no expert. I suggest letting the police make a determination.
不可能
Out of the question.
有几个原因说明这是不必要
That would be so unnecessary for any number of reasons...
不单只是为了克里斯先生的名誉
...not the least of which is Mr. Christian's reputation.
我们只想你找出拍这套影片的人
We want you to find out who made this film...
证实这是真是假
...and establish whether it's real.
你可以开个价钱
You can name your price.
我们会供应你买资料用的任何资源
You'll be provided with whatever you need to buy information.
那少女是唯一的线索
Girl's all I've got to go on.
我可以当它是一宗人口失踪案件
I could treat it like a missing persons case.
明白
Understood.
当然….
Of course...
我们要确保你不会拷贝这套影片
...we need to be assured that you would not copy this film.
我向你保证
You have my word on that.
我只向你汇报
But I'll be dealing directly with you...
只向你一个
...and only you.
你与你律师的关系如何是你的事
Your relationship with your attorney is your own.
-不是对你不礼貌 -不会
-No offense. -None taken.
我觉得你已经详细的考虑过
I realize you've given this careful consideration.
你可以毁灭它
You could have destroyed it.
告诉我这可怜的少女没有被杀
Tell me the poor girl wasn't killed.
求你
Please?
找到她要活着的
Find her alive.
我会尽力夫人
I'll do the best I can, ma'am.
你要去克利夫兰？
Cleveland?
你刚到家
You just got home.
我也希望可以留下 但这是房子的贷款
And I wish I could stay, but this is the mortgage.
仙蒂上大学的学费
It's Cindy's college money.
如果我办好这事 凭克里斯太太的社交圈子
If I do right by her, with the circle she runs in...
这会是一个难得的机会
...this could be a big break.
我不认为我们需要什么机会
I didn't know we needed a break.
你父亲认为我们需要
Your father seems to think we do.
那克里斯太太是怎样的人？
So, what was Mrs. Christian like?
就像你所想像的 我为她感到难过
Like you'd expect, I guess. I feel sorry for her.
那是宗人口失踪案
It's a missing persons.
我告诉她我会用两至三周时间
I told her I'd give it a couple, three weeks.
不该会用更多的时间 成功的机会不大
It can't take longer than that. It's an outside shot.
我只能告诉你这么多 你最好不要知道那么多
That's all I can tell you. Sometimes you can't know what I'm doing.
常常是这样
It's always that way.
她醒了我去看她
She's awake. I'll get her.
好吧我很快会上去
All right, I'll be up in a sec.
-你带枪？ -我不需要它
-You're taking the gun? -I won't need it.
那不要带
Don't take it.
我不会用它这只是作预防
I won't wear it. It's just a precaution.
别担心
Don't worry.
你到了那里会给我打电话吗？
Will you call me when you get there, please?
费城的一对医生夫妇聘请我
I've been hired by a couple in Philadelphia, a doctor and his wife.
几天前他们在81公路载了一名搭顺风车
A few days ago, they picked up a girl hitchhiking off 81...
约十八岁的离家出走少女
..a runaway, about 18, maybe.
他们请她吃饭
They buy her a meal.
那医生尝试劝她
The doctor tries to convince her...
最低限度给家里打个电话
...that, at the very least, she should call home.
不出意料 那女孩吃完
Not surprisingly, the girl ate, excused herself...
就找借口离开了
...that was the last they saw of her.
我有个在警局有关部门工作的朋友画了一张草图
We had a friend of mine at the department work up a sketch.
他们想看看我能否确认这少女
They want to see if I can ID this girl...
然后转告给她的父母
...then pass along a message to the parents...
让他们知道这孩子还活着
...letting them know the kid's alive.
你不介意我作核对？
You don't mind if I run a check?
请自便
Go ahead.
你想怎样就怎样
You want it, you got it.
随便找你需要的资料
Knock yourself out.
每年约有八十五万至一百万人失踪
Anywhere from 850,000 to 1,000,000 missing every year.
我们已尽量将资料存入电脑 其他的你就要翻看资料卡
We have as much as we can on computer, then it's the wet-thumb method.
档案根据失踪的州县及年份排列
Files are by state and year of disappearance.
我们把成年人和儿童分开
We keep children and adults separate.
请勿进食或吸烟
No eating or smoking.
-大厅有咖啡机 -味道好吗？
-The coffee machine's in the hall. -Any good?
很难喝
Horrible.
几天后它会成为你的好朋友
It'll be your best friend after a few days...
如果你撑到那么久
...if you last that long.
祝你好运
Good luck.
宝贝 是我
Honey, it's me.
你好吗？
How are you?
我很好
I'm good.
你在哪？
Where are you?
我还在克利夫兰仙蒂怎样？
I'm still in Cleveland. How's Cindy?
她很乖她在睡觉
She's sweet. She's sleeping.
我非常想你
I'm missing you bigtime.
我也很想你
Yeah, l miss you too.
我明天再打电话给你
I'll call you tomorrow.
好的晚安
Okay. Good night.
晚安甜心
Good night, sweetheart.
豪华544
喂 克里斯太太？ 汤姆·威尔斯
Hello, Mrs. Christian? Tom Welles.
进展是这样
Here's where we stand.
我查到那套影片的底片 型号是“豪华544”
l checked the film stock. It's called Supralux 544.
生产商在92年已经停止生产这型号的底片
The company that made that stock discontinued it in '92.
所以那套影片是在之前制作的
So the film was made prior to that.
我已经查得非常的仔细了
I'm probably being overly thorough with this...
但你可不可能找出你丈夫在六至七年前的
...but you might want to dig up your husband's financial records...
财政记录
...about 6 or 7 years ago.
看看有什么不寻常的地方
See if there's anything out of the ordinary.
很明显这不是一套你可以拿到快洗照相馆去冲洗的底片
Obviously, this isn't a movie you drop off at the one-hour photo.
那你认为这是唯一的拷贝
So you think it's one of a kind.
这个底片经过摄影机拍成的 是没有底片的
The film that went through the camera is what we've got. There's no negative.
不像录影带它不是可以随便复制的
Unlike video, it's not really designed to be duplicated.
无论如何我觉得….
Whatever this is, l have a feeling...
即使有拷贝流传 相信也不会有很多
...there aren't many copies floating around, if any.
我在找一个不确定是否失踪的少女
I'm looking for a girl we're not sure is missing.
发生在六七年前
With this happening 6 or 7 years ago...
找出制作这套影片的人
...finding the guys who made this film...
老实说将会是件很困难的事
...frankly, is going to be very difficult.
我知道你做得到你做得很好
l know you can do it. You're doing a wonderful job.
请告诉我你会继续调查
Please tell me you'll continue the investigation.
我会我会为你尽力去做
l will. I'll keep trying for you.
你可以信赖我 再见 克里斯太太
You can count on me. Goodbye, Mrs. Christian.
我们现在未能接听你的电话 请在讯号之后留下留言
We can't come to the phone right now, so please leave a message at the beep.
宝贝 是我
Honey, it's me.
对不起 我昨晚忘了打电话给你
I'm sorry I forgot to call last night.
我今晚不会忘记
I won't forget tonight.
我已经离家很久 我希望可以尽快回家
I've been gone a long time and I hope I'll be home soon.
我爱你 想你 今晚再谈
I love you, and I miss you. We'll talk tonight.
北卡罗莱纳
玛丽·安马修 16岁 1993年失踪
你找珍纳？
You looking for Janet?
你好 马修太太？
Hello, Mrs. Mathews?
我叫汤姆·贺特 我是州政府调查员
I'm Thomas Hart. I'm a state-licensed investigator.
我受雇于美国资源中心失踪人口部
I've been hired by the U.S. Resource Centre, Missing Persons...
现在做内部资料调查
..as part of an internal audit.
我想跟你约个时间
I'd like to make an appointment with you...
想问一些关于你女儿 玛丽·安的问题
...to answer questions about your daughter, Mary Anne.
我昨天跟联邦调查局的调查员….
I spoke to your FBI contact yesterday, Agent....
尼尔 尼尔·科尔？
Neil. Neil Cole?
对 科尔调查员 他会通知你我要来找你
Yes, Agent Cole. He told me he'd call and let you know to expect me.
他没有通知你？
He didn't call?
是你吗？
Is this you?
看来像五岁
You look about five years old.
不止五岁
A little older.
很可爱
Sweet.
最重要是….
It's important that...
你不要因我这次的查问而提高你的期望
...you don't let this raise your expectations.
也不会影响任何进行中的调查
It's not going to effect any ongoing efforts.
我想说的是
All I'm saying is, please know that...
我不是来带给你任何虚假的希望
...I'm not here to create any false hope.
我们一直在争吵玛丽·安和我
We fought all the time, Mary Anne and me...
和她的继父
...and her stepdad.
她憎恨他
She hated him...
因为他不是她的生父
...because he wasn't her real dad.
在家里和学校制造麻烦
Trouble here, trouble at school.
很麻烦
Trouble.
不喜欢规矩像我一样
Didn't like rules. Takes after me, I guess.
我从痛苦中学习
I had to learn the hard way.
我可以和你丈夫谈谈？
Can I speak to your husband?
她的继父？
Her stepfather?
大伟？
Dave?
死了
Gone.
是玛丽·安离家后两年
Two years after Mary Anne left.
她一直恨他
All the time, she resented him.
我因为他而失去她 然后我又失去他
I lost her because of him, and then I lost him.
现在只剩下我一个
I'm the only one still here.
玛丽·安有男朋友吗？
Did Mary have a boyfriend?
她有偷偷地和男孩子外出
She was sneaking out with someone.
她不会告诉我
She wouldn't tell me who.
满身吻痕的回家向我说谎
Coming home with hickeys, lying all the time.
我很抱歉向你提出 但在这种情况下
I am sorry to bring this up, but in these circumstances...
加上有继父
...with the stepfather....
有没有任何被性侵犯的迹像？
Were there any indications of any sort of abuse?
完全没有 警方和联邦调查局都问过
There was nothing like that. The police and FBI asked.
没有这种事发生过从来没有
Nothing happened like that. Never.
如果有她会告诉我
She'd have told me.
对不起 我不得不问
I apologize. I had to ask.
都是给她庆祝生日的 自从她离开后每年一份
Those are for her birthday. One for every year she missed.
都在等她回来
They'll be waiting for her when she comes back.
那是因为我打她巴掌
It's because I slapped her.
我知道
I know.
我们为了大卫吵架她激怒了我
We was fighting about Dave, and she was just pushing my buttons.
我便打她巴掌
And I slapped her.
天啊！
Jesus.
第二天她便走了
Next day, she was gone.
当孩子出走 他们几乎都会留下字条
When kids run, they almost always leave a note.
通常都会感到内疚
It's guilt, usually.
没有字条
There wasn't one.
警方查看过
Police looked.
诱拐和出走是两回事
An abduction's one thing, a runaway's another.
有时候离家出走都不是警方优先处理的案件
Sometimes it's not the priority for the police it should be.
没有留下任何东西 你不认为我会希望有吗？
There wasn't anything. Don't you think I wish there was?
你或许对但你会让我看看吗？
You're probably right, but would you let me look?
你告诉我….
You tell me...
不要存有太大希望
...not to get my hopes up...
也不要期望过高
...not to raise my expectations.
请自便
Go ahead.
我想喝点东西
I need a drink.
谢谢
Thank you.
亲爱的妈妈 假如你在看这信
Dear Mom: lf you're reading this...
大概是因为 我从加州的好莱坞打电话来
...it probably means l called you from Hollywood, California.
我留下日记 是因为我想让你知道 我为什么离开
l left my diary behind because l want you to see why I'm leaving.
不是因为你打我
It's not because you hit me.
我藏起这信 是不想让大卫这王八蛋找到
l hid this so Dave the dickhead wouldn't find it.
我和华伦·安迪生相爱
Warren Anderson and me are in love.
我要和他开始新生活
I'm going to start a whole new life with him.
华伦的父亲在镇上拥有一间车行
Warren's dad owns that garage in town.
但华伦有更大的志愿
But Warren has even bigger plans.
华伦要成为动作电影的巨星
Warren'll become a star in action movies.
他说我比很多电影里的女孩都漂亮
He says I'm prettier than a lot of girls in movies.
我也会成为巨星
I could be a star too.
要喝什么？
You want a drink?
当我们驶进好莱坞
When we cruise into Hollywood...
人人都感觉到我的眼睛在放光 因为我在恋爱中
...I'll have fiery eyes that everyone will notice, because l am in love.
你对我找不到任何资料
You were right. I didn't find anything.
为你准备了饮料
Fixed you a drink.
不 谢了 我还有工作要做
Thanks, no. I've got work to do.
我明天晚上再来
I'll stop by tomorrow night.
当你看这信时 我们可能已结婚了
We'll probably be married by the time you read this.
不要来找我 因为我不会回去
Don't come looking for me, because I'm not coming back.
或者有一天 你会在电视或杂志上看到我
Maybe someday you'll see me on TV or in magazines.
不要担心我 爱你的玛丽·安
Don't worry about me. Love, Mary Anne.
安迪生先生？
Mr. Anderson?
哪一位？
Who's asking?
汤姆·哈特 抱歉不能跟你握手
Tom Hart. Excuse me not shaking hands.
我想找你儿子 你有个儿子叫华伦 对吧？
I'm looking for your son. You've got a son named Warren, right?
对
Sure.
有什么事？
What's it about?
你是警察？
You a cop?
不是
No, sir.
是他一位老朋友 其实是欠了他一点钱
Just a friend from a while back. Owe him some money, actually.
你欠了他钱？
You owe him money?
这个倒新鲜
That's a new one.
如果你愿意你可以把钱交给我
You can leave it right here if you want.
假如你不介意 我想寄给他
If it's all the same, I'd like to send it to him.
加利福尼亚州对不对？
California, right?
加利福尼亚州？
California?
小子 你知道费亦威利监狱在哪里吗？
Son, you know where the Fayetteville lockup is?
华伦就在那里
That's where Warren is.
八个月的服刑期入屋行窃罪
Doing eight months on a B and E.
谢谢
Thank you.
唔 我认识她
Yeah, man, I knew her.
在我去洛杉矶之前 已经把那贱人甩了
Dumped that bitch right before I moved to L.A.
她来敲我门 像个他妈的贼婆娘
She shows up knocking at my door like a fucking stalker.
我叫那贱妇去死
Told that bitch she could go to hell.
她去了哪里？
Where'd she go?
可能是地狱
Hell, maybe.
我不知道 也没兴趣知道
I don't know and I don't give a fuck either.
她说她可能去脱衣舞酒吧工作
She said she might work at a titty bar or something.
其实她的胸并不迷人
Ask me, her tits weren't all that great.
你有再见她吗？
Did you hear from her again?
不要以为我干了她 就想让她跟我去好莱坞
Just because I was fucking her doesn't mean I wanted her out there.
她想在好莱坞成为巨星
She came to Hollywood to be a big fucking movie star.
我也一样
And so did I.
这就是现在的我
Check me out now.
为什么不给我一支烟？
Why don't you pass me one of them smokes?
我不吸烟
I don't smoke.
你好吗？
How you doing?
还可以
I'm okay.
你听起来不是很好
You don't sound okay.
事情并不简单
It's not easy.
为什么？发生什么事
Why? What's going on?
只是比我想像的更困难
It's tougher than I thought it would be, that's all.
是不是很辛苦？
Is it getting to you?
但我已有线索 不能放弃
l got a lead l can't drop.
我差不多完成了 想你
I'm almost done. I miss you.
我也想你 爱你
I miss you too. I love you.
替我亲一下仙蒂？
Give Cindy a kiss for me, okay?
等一下 她要跟你说再见 跟爹地说再见
Wait, I think she wants to say bye. Say bye to Daddy.
嗨 甜心
Hi, sweetie.
嗨 宝贝
Hi, honey.
嗨 仙蒂
Hi, Cinderella.
她正在摸电话
She's touching the phone.
你应该看看 她听见你声音时的表情
You should see her face at your voice.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你 再见
I love you too. Bye.
我正在做晚餐
I was just making dinner.
不知不觉地做了两人的份量
I've made enough for two, as it happens.
对不起 我不能留下
I'm sorry, I can't stay.
我只想让你知道 我跟我的人谈过
I wanted to let you know I spoke to my people at the agency.
我叫他们继续调查玛丽·安的案件
I told them to keep Mary Anne's case active.
那么…
Well...
起码 喝点东西吧
...stay for a drink, at least.
你确定不饿？
You sure you're not hungry?
偶尔吃一顿不看电视的晚餐也不错
It'd be nice to have a meal without the TV on for once.
我要开长途车
I have a long drive ahead of me.
一个人吃晚餐是最令人沮丧的事
It's one of the most depressing things. Eating alone.
我不知道为什么 你以为我应该已经习惯了
I don't know why. You'd think I'd be used to it by now.
马修太太
Mrs. Mathews?
珍纳
Janet.
你从来有没有想过
Do you ever consider....
有没有想过玛丽可能永远不回来了？
Do you realize that Mary may never come back?
我每天都在想
I think about it every day.
每一次电话响
Every time the phone rings...
每一次我都以为是她
...every time, I still think it's her.
她是我唯一所想的
She's all I think about.
你能告诉我
Can you tell me...
假如你要作出抉择 假如一定要你选择
...if you had to make a choice, if you were forced to choose...
一是幻想她在外面某处
...between imagining her out there somewhere...
过着很好的生活很快乐
...living a good life, being happy...
但你不知道
...but you don't know...
永远不会知道
...you never find out...
或是最坏的事实
...or the worst being true...
她已死了
...her being gone...
但你知道
...but you know.
你终于知道
You finally know...
她发生什么事
...what's happened to her.
我会怎样选？
What would I choose?
对
Yes.
我会选择去知道
I would choose to know.
我需要知道
I need to know.
对不起 我想借用你的洗手间
Excuse me, I have to use your restroom.
你要走了
You're leaving.
如果我有任何发现 我会通知你
I'll call you if I find anything out.
好莱坞
脱衣舞娘
成人书店
你好吗？
How you doing?
今晚有约会？
Big date tonight?
嗯 有可能
Yeah, guess so.
有没有兴趣看一个电动阴道？
Could I interest you in a battery-operated vagina?
很诱惑 但是不用了 谢谢
It's tempting, but no thanks.
我不想看到当你需要一个电动阴道
I'd hate to see you caught in one of those everyday situations...
而你没有的情况
...that calls for a battery-operated vagina and you don't have one.
我宁愿冒个险
I'll risk it.
没问题 一共是七十四元五毛八
All right, your total is $74.58 please.
一百元
A hundred.
二十五元和零钱
Total's $25 and some change.
多谢你在成人书店购物
I'd like to thank you for shopping at Adult Bookstore.
祝你有精彩的一天
And have yourself a fabulous day.
你在看什么？
What are you reading?
后庭花
很讨好的书名 你真正在看的是什么书？
Catchy title. What are you really reading?
很难相信这本书有任何值得强调的部份
Hard to believe it's got any parts worth highlighting.
冷血杀戮
卡波特
Capote.
你知道是怎样
You know how it is.
你不想在顾客面前令自己尴尬
Wouldn't want to embarrass yourself in front of your fellow perverts.
没错 我会被色情行业协会轰走
I might get drummed out of the pornographers' union.
那我靠什么生活？
Where would I be then?
祝今天愉快
Have a good day.
性爱不设防 性爱最过瘾
嗨 你好吗？
How are you?
嗨 宝贝
Hey, honey.
-你好吗？ -我有一点累
-How you doing? -I'm a little beat.
仙蒂怎样？
How's Cindy?
她很乖 她想念你
She's sweet. She misses you.
进展如何？
How's it going?
调查并不算很顺利 我现在只想着回家
The way things are going, I'm thinking about coming home.
真的？
Really?
宝贝 等一等
Honey, wait.
我再打给你好吗？
Can I call you back?
我答应马上打给你 再见 宝贝
I'll call you right back, l promise. Bye, honey.
克里斯太太 一共有三个人
Mrs. Christian, there were 3 men.
不单是那摄影师和戴面具的人
Not just the cameraman and the masked man.
我发现有第三个人在看
l caught a glimpse of a third man. He was watching.
我用电脑做一个比较清晰的影像
I'll try to get a clearer image through computer enhancement.
但这可能发生在六年前的事 所以并不是….
But this probably happened 6 years ago, so it's not--
好的 我会尽力
All right, I'll keep trying.
谢谢 谢谢你的支持
Thank you. l appreciate your support.
再见
Goodbye.
经过我们137个小时的工作
What we have here is 137 billable man-hours...
加上一部超过十万元的机器
...a hundred-plus thousand dollars machine...
得到的结果就是
...and the result is a...
一个放大了的男人头的背后
...fully rasterised enhancement of the back of some guy's head.
要不要裱起它？
Want it framed?
好的 祝你好运
There you go. Have a nice day.
这里像加油站 加油前要先付款
It's like a gas station, you pay before you pump.
记得我吗？
Remember me?
回来买那电动阴道吗
Came back for the battery-operated vagina after all.
我想要一些资料 也许你能帮忙
I need information. Maybe you could help.
托马斯·威尔斯 照片很漂亮
Thomas Welles. Nice picture.
哪一种资料？因为我有各方面的
What sort of information? Because I got all different kinds.
我会付钱的那种
The kind I'll pay for.
我不知道你在找哪一种….
I don't know what you're looking for...
先说清楚 我不是同性恋
...so we're clear from the start, I'm straight.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
谢谢
Thank you.
拉上拉链！
Zip it!
我可以提供资料
I can hook you up.
你说出要我做的 我给你报价
You name the vice, I name the price.
你在这里工作了多久？
How long you been working here?
大约两年
Almost two years.
你叫什么名字？如果你不介意我问
What's your name, if you don't mind me asking?
麦克斯
Max.
这是我们的交易
Here's the deal.
我正在调查有关地下色情行业
This thing I'm on now has to do
with underground pornography.
非法在台底交易的那种东西
Stuff that's sold under
the counter, illegally.
没有什么非法的东西
There's not much illegal out there.
不管有多少
我都要知道要查清楚
Whatever there is, I want to know.
I want a good look.
如果你有这些门路很好
如果没有请你立刻说
So if you've got that kind of
connection, great. If not, speak now.
你是警察？
You're not a cop, are you?
如果你是你必须告诉我
If I ask and you are,
you got to tell me.
我不是警察
I'm not a cop.
私家侦探？
A private detective?
像夏飞特？
Like Shaft?
有否看过私家真棒？
我有减价发售
You ever seen Private Dicks?
I got it on sale.
你在这里赚多少钱？
How much you make in there?
约四百元一个星期不用交税
Around 400 bucks a week,
off the books.
假设我生活在
与你相同的幻想世界
Let's pretend I live
in the same fantasy world...
而你在这垃圾地方
每星期赚四百元
...where you make ＄400
a week in that dump.
我给你五百元工作几天
I'll give you 500 for a few days.
六百吧阿伯
Six sounds good, Pops.
五百
Five.
这是我的电话号码
Here's my number.
你何时可以开始？
When can you start?
嗯明天晚上我很晚下班
Well, tomorrow night I get off late.
明天见
Tomorrow.
好吧
All right.
不要叫我阿伯
And don't call me Pops.
当然我不想伤害你的感情
Of course not. I wouldn't
want to hurt your feelings.
我不知道你的性趣
Look, l don't know
what your scene is.
你可能和其他人一样喜欢色情
You may like porn
as much as the next guy.
但你不太像一般喜欢这玩意的人
But you don't look
like your average sleaze.
反而像个警察
More like your average fucking cop.
所以当你问及那些
非法的东西的时候
So when you ask people about fucking
illegal stuff, it has a certain...
你有种特别的神情
...patina to it.
神情
Patina.
那是卡波特词语
懂吗？
It's a Truman Capote word.
Hello?
如果从没人看过
或卖过这类电影
If someone never saw
or sold a snuff film...
他们不会在乎我问什么
...they shouldn't care
what I ask.
如果他们有就会比较紧张
If they have,
they should be nervous.
只要你觉得谁有嫌疑
不要放弃
Whoever acts insulted,
keep knocking on their door.
这阿伯现在改变初衷
还不是太迟
Look, Pops, it's not too late
to change your mind about all this.
你将会见到一些
你不忘记的东西
There's things you're going
to see that you can't unsee.
会让你印象很深刻
They get in your head and stay there.
你怎知道我看过什么？
How do you know what I've seen?
那很好但每个人都有他的极限
Okay, fine.
But everybody's got their limit.
我在这里呆了他妈的六年
尝试发展我的音乐事业
I've been here 6 fucking years
trying to get my music together.
所以我开始兼职以维持生计
So I start part-time
where I work to make ends meet.
一晃眼几年光景过去
我仍是老样子
And boom, a couple years go by,
and here I am.
只是说在你发觉以前
你已经成为这行业的一份子
I'm just saying, before you know it,
you're in it. Deep in it.
别为我担心
Don't worry about me.
谢谢你
But thank you.
别客气
You're welcome.
阿伯你在和魔鬼共舞
魔鬼不会改变
Pops, you dance with the devil,
the devil don't change.
魔鬼会改变你
Devil changes you.
你歌词的部份？
Some of your lyrics?
很好笑
That's cute.
这地方已存在约有三年
This place has been around
about 3 years...
但他们不断搬来搬去
...but they keep moving it
house to house.
这只是一小部份
This is the tip of the iceberg.
有很多墨西哥性虐待
有很多亚洲性奴
Lots of Mexican S & M,
lots of Asian bondage...
各种的兽行如果你有兴趣的话
...all kinds of bestiality,
if you're into that.
别碰任何东西
想要什么告诉飞弟
Don't touch nothing.
You want something, tell Friendly.
问他看看？
Ask him.
别这样！
Don't do that!
好了！没事！
All right! It's cool!
没问题？
All right? Okay.
走吧好的
Come on, let's go.
All right!
你是不是一个法律执行人
或与法律执行有关？
Are you a law enforcement agent
or affillated with law enforcement?
操你赖瑞
Fuck you, Larry.
你是否一个法律执行人
或与法律执行有关？
Are you a law enforcement agent,
or affillated with law enforcement?
操你赖瑞
Fuck you, Lar.
你越来越上道了威尔斯
You're getting cool there, Welles.
这里有你那色情电影的怪人
卖那些烫手货的人
You got your porn zombies here.
Junkies for the hard stuff.
但这种地下室销售不会维持很久
But these basement sales
won't last much longer.
一太冒险
二所有东西都上网
One, it's too risky.
And two, everything's on the Net.
嫖客在网上交换照片
Chicken hawks swapping photos
with their modems.
分类广告有密码
Then there's classified ads
with hidden codes, secret couriers...
由假的公司秘密递送
...wires through dummy corporations.
有什么不合法的
顾客都跑得远远的
If something's illegal, the buyers
are as far away as they can get.
大家互不认识你明白我说什么
Nobody knows what nobody knows,
you know what I mean?
你好吗山美？
How's it going, Samuel?
我去跟她打招呼
I'm going to say hi to her.
你好吗？我喜欢
How are you? I love that.
是有拉链的麦克杰克森像
It's the Michael Jackson look,
with the zippers.
儿童
这是什么？
What are these?
极度性奴
Extreme bondage.
强奸电影
Rape films.
恶心到极点
Sick shit.
买五送一
Buy five, get one for free.
有没有更精彩的？
Anything harder?
没有更精彩的
There's nothing harder.
色情暴力电影？
Snuff?
没有这种电影
There's no such thing as snuff.
先生你看到的就是我所有的
What you see is what I got, mister.
我在哪里可以找到？
我有很多钱
Do you know where I can get some?
I have a lot of money.
操你
Fuck off.
就是她
There she is.
就是她“重掴桃乐菲”
It's Double Slap Dorothy.
这个女人可以成为垒球员
There's one chick that
could be a baseball player.
她的臂力很惊人
The swing on her is unreal.
有些色情暴力电影
是界乎于三级片与暴力之间
Some of these S & M and bondage films
you'll see straddle the line.
恋足狂集体性交
Foot fetish, orgies, shit films...
雌雄同体伤残
比三级片更精彩
...hermaphrodites, mutilation.
It's harder than hard-core.
但大部份是合法
But mostly legal.
阴茎
Stick.
有人见到觉得呕心
One guy sees it and pukes.
有人见到却爱到死
Another guy sees it
and he falls in love.
这是我跟你提的那个人
你有带子吗？
This is the guy I was telling you about.
You got the tapes?
一千元
A thousand bucks.
-一千二佰元两盒
-你对麦克斯说一千
-1 200 for the two.
-You told Max 1 000.
我知道但这个更有趣
我抬高价钱你就会不爽
I know, but this is more fun. I raise
the price, and you get pissed off.
-我以为我们已经说好
-那是真的吗？
-I thought we had a relationship.
-Is it real?
从来没见过这样恶心的
Sickest shit you'll ever see.
是真的吗？
Is that real?
看起来他妈的是真的
That sure as shit looks real.
她没有了呼吸
She's not breathing.
这影片是谁制作？
Who makes these films?
我不知道
I don't know.
好像是菲律宾人
Looks like the Philippines.
对肯定是菲律宾人
Yeah, definitely the Philippines.
等等是同一个女孩
Wait a minute.
That's the same girl.
是同一个女孩吗？
Isn't that the same girl?
看
Look.
是同一个女孩
It is the same.
那是假的
They're fakes.
真棒
That's great.
残杀2：重生
Snuff 2: The Resurrection.
我的天
Oh, boy.
付1200元你期望什么？
Well, what do you expect for 1 200?
你想喝点啤酒或什么？
我想喝点酒精饮料
You want a beer or something?
I could use anything.
对不起我要告诉你
色情暴力电影是不存在的
But I'm sorry, man.
I told you snuff was bogus.
我希望我有替你拿收据
I just wish I would have
gotten you a receipt.
“重重一击”
''Hard Spank.''
“麦克斯加利福尼亚”
''Max California.''
那是我以前的乐队
That's my old band.
我们已拆伙了
We broke up.
什么时候？
When?
大约一年前
Maybe about a year ago.
我不是想侮辱你
I don't mean any offense...
但你在这行业里混什么？
...but what are you doing
mixed up in all this?
我并没有在混什么阿伯
I'm not mixed up in anything, Pops.
你让我觉得你很聪明
可以做其他的事
You strike me as being smart enough
to do something else.
谢谢
Thanks.
我希望你拥有一间唱片公司
I wish you owned a record label.
起码比在加油站工作好得多
Look, it beats pumping gas.
但自己不买也不赞同
I don't buy it.
I don't endorse it.
我只是指点客人迷津
I just point the way.
但你说这让你沮丧
You said it gets to you.
嗯该死的可以这么说！
Well, hell, yeah!
我每天看到多少痞子？
Parade of losers I see every day?
我有什么选择？
What choices have I got?
音乐界并没有真正敲我的门
The music industry is not exactly
beating down my door.
你呢汤威尔斯？
And what about you, Tom Welles?
你戴有戒指你有小孩？
You got a ring on your finger.
You got kids?
一个女儿
A daughter.
那你有一位太太和一个女儿
So you got a wife and a daughter...
和一间不错的小黄屋
...and a nice little yellow house...
和一只狗
...and a dog named Shep.
那你在这里做什么？
What the hell are you doing here?
问得好
Good question.
你在像今晚的地方
感到兴奋吗？
Do you get turned on
at places like tonight?
我没有
No, I am not.
你也不会完全没感觉
You don't exactly
get turned off, either.
魔鬼已经在改变你
Devil's changing you already.
晚安麦克斯
Good night, Max.
收容所
这位先生想问有没有人
认得这位少女
This gentleman was asking if anyone
recognizes this girl.
我记得
Yes.
她是玛丽·安
I remember Mary.
玛丽·安马修？
Mary Anne Mathews?
如果没有记错她在这里住了
大概一个月
She lived here for only about a month,
if I recall correctly.
有个晚上她没有回来
你知道她发生什么事？
She didn't return one night.
Do you know what happened to her?
还不知道我现在为她母亲在找她
Not yet, but I'm looking
into it for her parents.
请你把那有花的箱子拿下来？
Could you get
that flowered one down for me?
这是她的箱子
That's her suitcase.
我已经忘记了
直到你给我看她的照片
I'd forgotten about it
till you showed me her picture.
我希望她会回来
I suppose I always
hoped she'd be back.
她好像很迷失
She seemed so lost.
之后我只能祈祷
她有更好的出路
After a time, all I could do was pray
she'd moved on to better things.
你能把这个拿给她的家人吗？
Can you get this suitcase
to her people?
如果适当的话
If it's approprlate.
当然没问题谢谢你
Yes, of course. Thank you.
星光闪闪星光亮
Starlight, star bright
今晚我看到的第一颗星
First star I've seen tonight
我希望我可以希望我可能
l wish l may, wish l might
让我今晚梦想成真
Have this wish l wish tonight
这号码已暂停使用
This number has been disconnected
or is no longer in service.
喂好莱坞腊像馆
有什么可以帮你？
Hello, Hollywood Wax Museum.
Can l help you?
这是接线生149
城市和名称？
This is operator 149.
What city and listing?
我不知道只知是好莱坞
l don't know. Hollywood.
叫做名人电影
我想要地址
A listing for Celebrity Films,
and l need an address.
要电话号码和地址请不要挂断
Please hold for
phone number and address.
名人电影404
爱迪普利
我先到的
I was here first.
对不起我只需要几分钟
Sorry, I'll just be a couple minutes.
爱迪普利？
Eddie Poole?
你是诉讼通知书送递员？
You a process server?
不我一直在查问
你有没有见过….
No, I've been inquirlng around.
Have you seen...
这少女来这里应征？
...this girl come through here.?
你是警察？
You a cop?
我是她的家人
I'm a member of her family.
你知道有多少少女在这里出入？
You know how much pussy
comes through here?
请你看一眼可能有好几年了
Please, if you'd just take a look.
It would've been a few years.
她叫玛丽·安马修
Her name is Mary Anne Mathews.
没见过
Never seen her.
你肯定？
You sure?
我刚才不是已看过那
他妈的照片吗？
I just looked
at the fucking picture, didn't I?
好了
我还有很多他妈的事要做
Now come on.
I got a lot of shit to do.
下一位
Who's next?
没问题
This'll be fine.
你卖他妈的什么？
What kind of shit are you peddling?
我的带子很受欢迎
他们很喜欢
Come on. My tapes sell.
People eat the shit up.
上个月有三个无赖来退钱
l had three jerks trying
to return your tapes last month.
你知道有多烂
才有混球回过头来
You know how bad it has to be
for some jackass to come back...
拿着他妈的收据
要退他妈的钱？
...with a fucking receipt
and try to fucking return it?
有多烂？
How bad?
拍些高档货
找些还有牙齿的女孩
Get together some upscale product
where the girls still have teeth.
我操你！
Till then, fuck you!
你老妈还有没有牙齿？
Does your mother have any teeth?
如果有叫她来去你的
Because if she does,
send her down, you fuck.
他没有接听
He's not answering.
嘿老板
Hey, boss.
这里有啤酒
There's a case of beer in there.
今天好吗？
How's your day?
好
Great.
人到齐吗？
Is everybody here?
人到齐除了那其中一个少女
Everybody but one of the chicks.
-还在监视她们？
-对干嘛？
-Been watching them?
-Yeah. Why?
名人电影
Celebrity Films.
我什么都知道
I know all about it.
嗯你知道什么？
Yeah, you know about what?
关于那女孩
About that girl...
六年前
...six years ago.
我知道你对她做过什么
I know what you did to her.
你是谁？
Who is this?
你杀了她
You murdered her.
你和你的朋友
You and your friends.
我不知道你他妈的说什么
l don't know what the fuck
you're talking about.
你在影片里杀死她
You killed her on film.
现在你有麻烦
And now you're fucked.You're all fucked.
你们全部有麻烦
You're all fucked.
快点
Come on.
快点给我一点线索爱迪
Come on, give me something, Eddie.
是我
It's me.
你有什么事？
What do you want?
我刚接到个电话
Look, l just got a phone call.
我们要谈谈
但不方便在电话里谈
We got to talk.
And we can't talk on the phone.
所以我们其中一个需要坐上飞机
So one of us
has to get on a plane, all right?
去你的你这神经过敏的疯子
Blow me, you paranoid fuck.
他妈的
Fuck! Fuck!
你喜欢看你这神经过敏的疯子
So you like to watch, paranoid fuck.
电话是登记在
曼哈顿帝诺伟域的名下
Phone is listed under ''D. Velvet''
in Manhattan.
帝诺伟域
Dino Velvet.
他是制片人/导演/怪人
He's a producer/director/weirdo.
他像性虐待的贾慕思
He's like the Jim Jarmusch of S & M.
他的作品有多刺激？
How hard is his stuff?
你想有多刺激？
How hard do you want it?
性奴恋物狂诡异香辣片
Bondage, fetish, Gothic hard-core.
肯定不是给神经质看的
Definitely not for the squeamish.
并不容易找得到
It's kind of hard to come by.
通常透过性杂志封底订购
Mostly out of the back
of bondage magazines.
但他有崇拜者
But he's got fans.
我认识一个人
认为那是艺术
This guy I know, he thinks it's art.
他告诉我如果有足够的钱
伟域会受托拍电影的
He's told me Velvet will do
commissions if there's enough dough.
刚好在合法与不合法的边缘
Nothing illegal, but borderline.
如果有人想看一个穿潜水衣
的人妖
If a guy wants to see
a transvestite in a rubber suit--
我明白
I got the picture.
麦克斯进来
Max, get in here!
那….
So...
你要去纽约吗？
...you're going to New York?
可能
Maybe.
你这个样子
Looking like that.
你会需要我
You'll need me.
我认识这人范炽
他不仅是伟域电影迷那么简单
This guy I know, Frenchie, is more
than just a fan of Velvet films.
如果你想我可以带你去
I could get you in if you want.
当然要多点钱
For more money, of course.
还有出差费我要坐头等
Plus expenses. I fly first class.
我们何时出发？
So when are we leaving?
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
哗这是我第一次来纽约
Man, my first time in
the Big Bad Apple.
不要拍我
I told you, don't film me.
好霍华休斯
Fine, Howard Hughes.
你没告诉我会这样豪华
You didn't say it was going to be
this luxurious.
这是总统套房
It's the Presidential suite.
你有令人舒服的幽默感
You have a comforting
sense of humour.
我在隔壁几间房
I'll be a couple of doors down.
汤姆我不知为什么要住
这种廉价旅馆
Tom, I don't know why
we're staying in this fleabag.
在廉价旅馆
人们才不会管闲事
People mind
their own business in fleabags.
我现在出去一会
你找一下伟域的录影带
I'm going out. Dig up
whatever Velvet tapes you can find.
拿收据
Get receipts.
知道
Yes, sir.
我丈夫有五个现金户口
My husband had
five cash accounts he used.
在1992年
Between November...
十一月
...of 1 992...
到1993年的
...and March...
三月之间
...of 1 993...
他从每一个户口
开出一张现金支票
...he wrote one check
out to cash from each account.
我丈夫从来不亲自处理钱的事
My husband never dealt with money
personally.
尤其是现金
Certainly not cash.
这五张支票的总数很惊人
These checks he wrote
are for very odd amounts.
全部加起来
When totaled together...
这五张支票
...the five checks...
从五个不同的户口提取了
...from the five different accounts...
总共一百万
...they equal ＄1 million.
克里斯太太那很有趣
That is interesting, Mrs. Christian.
我提及这是因为
I only mentioned this because...
你叫我看看有什么
不寻常的地方
...you asked me to look
for anything unusual.
我现在剩下五千元现金
I've got about ＄5,000 left in cash.
如果你批准我跟你提出的计划
我还需要五万元
I'll need another 50, if you approve
the plan I mentioned earlier.
我快可辨认出那戴面具
男人的身份了
I'm very close to establishing
the identity of the man in the mask.
我会叫朗先生安排
I'll have Mr. Longdale arrange it.
怎样交给你？
How will l get it to you?
如果你有笔我给你地址
If you have a pen,
I'll give you the address.
欢迎来到帝诺伟域的世界
Welcome to the world of Dino Velvet.
他是谁？戴面具的他是谁？
Who is this? In the mask, who is he?
来吧醒醒他是谁？
Come on, wake up. Who is this?
是帝诺常用的疯子
他常常出现在帝诺的电影里
One of the lunatics Dino always uses.
He's in a bunch of these.
他叫什么名字？
What's his name?
不知道这是他的特点
I don't know. That's his whole thing.
他经常戴面具
He always wears a mask.
他叫自己“兵器”
He calls himself ''Machete.''
不是“机器”
No, ''Machine.''
他叫自己“机器”
He calls himself Machine.
他是个工作狂
He's a lover, man.
他绝对热爱他的工作
Definitely loves what he does
for a living.
我希望我也可以这样说你
I wish I could say the same about you.
是是
Yes, yes.
我可以感觉到他们
非常欣赏我的风格
I can see they
really appreclate my style here.
我可以马上跟群众打成一片
I kind of blend in with the crowd here.
可能你没留意
If you didn't notice.
像这里的女士
她们喜欢我的风格
Like these ladies here,
they like my style.
这是谁？
Who is it?
麦克斯加利福尼亚
Yes, this is Max California.
我打过电话来
我是范炽在洛杉矶的朋友
I called earlier.
I'm a friend of Frenchie's from L.A.
我和我的合伙人想见伟域先生
My partner and I
would like to speak to Mr. Velvet.
他不在这里
He's not here.
我们有一笔钱给他
We're here to give him
a large sum of money.
如果没兴趣
我们就走了
If he's not interested, we'll split.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talk about.
你能回答我的简单问题吗？
Can't you just answer
my simple question?
我问你罗拉他妈的在哪里？！
I asked you a question!
Where the fuck is Laura?!
那是我过去十分钟
一直问你的问题
That's what I've been asking you
the last 1 0 minutes.
请坐不要客气
Sit down. Make yourself comfortable.
你这呆子！
You idiot!
两天后拍摄？
Going to shoot in two days?
喂你在乱花我的钱
Man, you're spending my money.
嗯你最好这样
Yeah, you better do that.
操你的
Fucking asshole.
很荣幸认识你
谢谢你接见我们
It's an honour to meet you.
Thank you for seeing us.
天啊
God.
那我可以有什么效劳？
So, what can I do you for?
我们想委托你制作一套影片
一套独一无二的帝诺伟域影片
We'd like to commission a film.
A Dino Velvet original, one of a kind.
对
That's right.
我很崇拜你
I'm a huge admirer of yours.
天我爱被人捧
God, I love flattery.
你是个天才伟域先生
一个不可多得的天才
You're a genius, Mr. Velvet.
A goddamn genius.
唯一仍然用底片拍成录影带
The only one still transferring film
to video.
再没有人欣赏这种诚意
Nobody really appreclates
that kind of integrity anymore.
你电影所表现的狂妄气质
The grain and the gritty look you get.
那套是你的至爱？
Which is your favourite?
如果我要选
If I had to choose...
那一定是窒息或魔鬼
...it'd be Choke or Devil.
那种潜意识意像
The subliminal imagery...
在窒息里真正令你毛骨悚然
...in Choke is what
really gets under your skin.
而魔鬼令我害怕也令我兴奋
Well, Devil frightened me
as much as it excited me...
但很难去选一套最爱
...but I'd be hard-pressed
to choose a favourite.
预算是多少？
What kind of a budget
are we talking about?
预付五千
Five thousand now.
完成后再付五千
Five thousand upon delivery.
两个女人一个黑一个白
Two women. One white, one black.
性奴当然
Hard bondage, of course.
除了这我信任….
Other than that, trusting your...
你的艺术表达
...artistic interpretation...
我只有两个条件
...I only have two stipulations.
尽管说
Challenge me.
我要看着你们工作
I want to watch you work.
你要不要特许经营权？
You don't want a franchise, do you?
偷取我泡制火辣辣酱料
Steal the recipe for my secret...
的秘方？
...hot sauce?
不要
No.
那很好
That's good.
我谢谢你
I appreclate that.
第二条件
Second stipulation.
另外那演员
The other performer...
必须是….
...has to be...
你用的那野兽….
...that animal you use.
戴面具的男人
The man in the mask.
机器
Machine.
我不知道
I don't know.
他可能有兴趣
He might be interested.
我想我要多收你….
But I think it'll cost you another...
五到七千元
...five to seven grand.
如果你多付一万
我可以安排更特别的东西
I can arrange something
really special for ten.
我可以去安排
We can do that.
那很好
Good enough for me.
我要开始构思
I'll just have to put
my thinking cap on.
我会收起这个当订金
I'm going to keep this as a deposit.
记得今晚十点后打电话给我
You make sure you call me
after 1 0 o'clock tonight.
十点
1 0 o'clock.
你知道吗你有张很特别
You know, you have a very special...
很漂亮的脸
...very beautiful face.
尤其当光反射在你脸上时
The way light hits it.
我想拍你
I'd like to shoot you.
你不介意吧？
You don't mind?
我怕见镜头
I'm camera-shy.
你信任我让我拿走你的钱
却不让我拍照
You trust me to take your money,
but not your picture?
那是两种不同的信任
Those are two different kinds of trust.
希望我们可以合作做生意
I hope we can do business.
何特街布鲁克林三点
Hoyt Avenue, Brooklyn, 3 o'clock.
我会到
I'll be there.
我还有事谢谢
I got something to tend to. Thanks.
我们是否要拍电影？
So are we in the movie business?
这是给你的
That's for you.
是什么？
What is it?
钱人们买东西用的
Money.
People use it to purchase goods.
那很慷慨但….
That's awfully generous
and everything--
不是我的不要当作什么大事
It's not mine.
Don't make a big deal out of it.
有班飞机和这机票
你今晚可以回洛杉矶
There's a plane ticket and the flight
you can catch to L.A. tonight.
我要你做的就是这么多
This is as far as I want you to go.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
我们是一伙的
我们是合伙人
We're a team. We're partners.
麦克斯我肯定你知道
跟我们周旋的这些人
Max, I'm sure you realize
these people we're dealing with...
他们是极度没人性的
...they're extremely disturbed.
所以你需要我
我了解他们你看我
That's why you need me.
I know disturbed. Look at me.
你做得很好但是时候回家
You did a great job here.
It's time for you to go home.
但这是我们的大案子
But this is our big case.
汤姆我知道发生什么事？
Tom, I know what's going on, okay?
什么事？
Okay, what?
帝诺和机器和爱迪
制作一套色情暴力电影对吗？
Dino and Machine and Eddie
made a snuff film, right?
我弄不清为什么你会参与其中
I can't figure out why you're involved.
或者这受害人….？
What, maybe the victim--?
第一谁说你对？
First, who said you're right?
第二谁说有受害人？
Second, who said
anything about a victim?
汤威尔斯生命只有三条规条
Only 3 rules in life, Tom Welles.
一永远有受害人
二不要做受害人
One, there's always a victim.
And two, don't be it.
三呢？
And three?
忘记三是什么了
I forgot three.
好我希望你忘记一切
Good, I want you to forget everything.
我要你上飞机
回洛杉矶并忘记一切
I want you to get on a plane,
go back to L.A. and forget it all.
我在西岸工作的机会很多
I get a lot of calls for work
on the West Coast.
我会再打电话给你
请你帮忙
I'd like to call you again.
I could use help.
你会再跟我联络吧？
You're going to look me up and call me?
我要你帮我我认为你很机伶
I could use your help. I meant it
when I said I think you're smart.
我不是对你施恩
I'm not patronizing you.
那谢谢你
Well, thanks.
好你保重麦克斯
All right.
Well, you take care, Max California.
好的汤威尔斯
魔鬼在等着你
All right, Tom Welles.
Devil's waiting on you.
你来了
There you are.
来加入我们
Come and join us.
嗨机器
Hello, Machine.
喜欢你的工作
Love your work.
有带钱来吗？
Did you bring the money?
在这里
It's right here.
好
Good.
女人在哪里？
Where are the women?
女人….
Women...
她们常常迟到
...they're always late.
这是做什么？
What are these for?
只是道具
They're just props.
很漂亮对不对？
Nice, aren't they?
机器和我刚刚在讨论刀的美
Machine and I were just talking
about the beauty of knives.
我的客人来了
My guests have arrived!
W先生可不可以请你
Mister W., would you be so kind...
放下身上的枪械？
...as to remove
any firearms from your person?
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
我很讨厌重覆自己
这让我看起来很笨
I hate to repeat myself.
It makes me look so stupid.
慢慢来
Slowly.
请给我看你的枪
Please, show me your gun.
别紧张！
Nice and easy!
对别紧张
That's right. Easy.
好
Good.
把子弹拿出来放在台上
Now empty those bullets onto the table.
很小心地
Very carefully.
-我不知道为何你会以为….
-住口他妈的
-I don't know why you think--
-Shut up, you fuck!
我会一箭
穿过你他妈的喉咙明白吗？
I'll put an arrow right through
your goddamn throat, you understand?
就是他
That's him.
最后的子弹
最后一颗
Last bullet. That's last one.
乖孩子
Good boy.
爱迪把他铐在床上
Now cuff him to the bed, Eddie.
是的
Yes, sir.
机器
Machine!
刚开始我不知道对你如何评价
I didn't know
what to make of you at first.
而你肯定令到爱迪如坐针毯
And you certainly had Eddie here
on pins and needles.
看哪在意料之外….
Lo and behold,
from right out of the blue came...
有我们以前生意的伙伴
来解释一切
..an old business acquaintance of ours
to explain everything.
机器之神来解疑难
Satan ex machina.
你记得朗先生吗？
You remember Mr. Longdale, don't you?
让我们解决他
Let's get this over with.
住口没人跟你说话
Shut up. Nobody's talking to you.
这些脸孔
在影片里可以做什么
What I could do
with faces like these on film.
但我回头想
我为何需要他们的脸孔？
But on second thought,
why would I need their faces?
你要听我说
You're going to listen to me.
你去取那影片
You're going to get that film.
你去将那影片拿回来交给我
You're going to
bring it back here, give it to me.
效率越高的话
Just so we make this
as efficient as possible...
我会重重有赏
...there is an incentive.
这与他无关
He's got nothing to do with this.
他什么都不知道
He doesn't know anything.
你想到我接着想说什么？！
Can't you guess
what I'm about to say next?!
如果你不将那影片拿回来给我
If you don't bring me that film...
我们会杀死他操他
...we're going to kill him, fuck him...
并拍摄全程
...and film it.
如果这还不够
If that's not enough for you...
我们打算去找你的家人
...we're going to go after your family.
我去取影片
I'll get the film.
乖孩子
Good boy.
你非常合作
You're being very cooperative.
朗先生会陪着你
Mr. Longdale here
will keep you company.
为什么是我？
Why me?
因为我不喜欢你朗先生
Because I don't like you, Mr. Longdale.
W先生
Mr. W...
快回来
...hurry back.
从我一见你你并没有做过什么
Since I met you,
there isn't much you've done...
我也没有理会
...that I haven't been party to.
如果你放弃并退出
就没有事会发生
None of this would be happening
if you'd given up and walked away.
更理想的是
一开始你就没有接这工作
Or better yet,
not taken the job in the first place.
我没有想到你会查的这么深入
I never expected you to get this far.
我聘请你因为你年青
I hired you because you're young...
肯定不会成功
..and completely out of your league.
但我低估了你的野心
But I underestimated your ambition.
你看过克里斯家的豪宅
You took one look
at the Christian compound.
很让你羡慕吧？
It was heady, wasn't it?
这次你不只是在门口张望
You weren't just peeking through
the gates this time.
不克里斯太太邀请你进入
No, Mrs. Christian welcomed you in.
你会以为克里斯太太聘请我们
Do you think people like
the Christians hire people like us...
便会邀请我们去晚宴？
...as an invitation
to their dinner parties?
我们要为他们收拾烂摊子
No, we're there to clean up the mess...
替他们收拾残局
...to wipe their royal asses.
叫你去买套色情暴力电影
You were asked to buy a snuff film.
他们找不到
你就付钱去制作一套？
They couldn't find one,
so you paid them to make you one?
情况是不是这样？
Isn't that what happened?
她本来是活生生的
你付钱让他们把她杀掉？
She was alive
till you paid to have her murdered?
克里斯先生付了多少钱
给你的良知？
How much did Christian
pay for your conscience?
一百万？
A million?
我已经得到补偿
I've been well compensated.
但你我廉价请你
But you, I bought cheap.
因为克里斯太太赞赏你的谨慎
Just because Mrs. Christian
praised your discretion...
便把这谋杀案的证物给你
...you sat on evidence of murder.
你将你的朋友家人
Dragged your friend, family...
拖进坟墓里
...into some old graveyard...
将一个没人理会或记得的
死掉少女发掘出来
...to dig up a dead girl with no name
that nobody cares about or remembers.
玛丽·安马修
Mary Anne Mathews.
那是她的名字
That was her name.
她母亲记得她
Her mother remembers her.
我觉得厌烦
I'm bored with this.
你知道我们之间的不同处？
You know the only difference
between us?
我会因这事继续生存
并从中获利而你….
I will survive this and profit by it,
whereas you...
你却不会
...you will not.
现在去取影片
Now get the film.
你有和他一起看？
Did you watch it with him?
什么？
What?
那影片你有和他一起看吗？
The snuff film.
Did you watch it with him?
这帮不到你的朋友去取影片
This isn't helping your friend.
Get the film.
他有感到兴奋？
Did it get him off?
克里斯先生？
Mr. Christian?
看着他们把她切开
他有手淫吗？
Watching them cut her up like that?
Did he jerk off to it?
你有握他的阴茎替他手淫？
Did you hold his cock?
Give him the hand job...
当看着玛丽·安马修死亡？
..while Mary Anne Mathews was dying?
-你想做什么？
-我尝试去明白
-What are you doing?
-I'm trying to understand!
他要一套色情暴力电影做什么？！
What did he want with a snuff film?!
你在问为什么？
You're asking why?
对为什么？为什么？！
Yes, why? Why?!
他为什么要一套….
Why did he want a film...
少女被剖开的影片？！
...of a little girl being butchered?!
因为他有能力
Because he could.
他这样做因为他有能力
He did it because he could.
你在找什么其他原因？
What other reason
were you looking for?
快
Now.
这里
Here.
射我
Shoot me.
威尔斯先生影片请
Mr. Welles, the film, please.
先让他走
Let him go first.
随你喜欢怎样处置我
总之让他走
Do whatever you want to me,
but let him go.
好的放开他机器
Very well. Set him free, Machine.
-是这个吗？
-是这个
-Is that it?
-That's it.
太好了
Bravo.
我不觉得你会想错过这一段
I don't think you want to miss this...
威尔斯先生
...Mr. Welles.
事件完结
So it ends.
就像她从来没有存在过
As if she never existed.
不要埋怨自己
你不能控制大局
Don't blame yourself.
You were in way over your head.
你这卑鄙小人
You motherfuckers.
你这下流的混帐东西
You smalltime motherfuckers.
我想知道
I want to know something:
你们有一百万去分为什么
还是下流的贱货？！
Why you're still smalltime with a
million dollars to spread around?!
一百万？
Million?
对那是克里斯家给朗的！
Yeah! That's what Christian
gave Longdale!
那是他给你的对不对？
That's what he gave you, right?
一百万现金？
A million in cash?
你这白痴他妈的垃圾！
You stupid fucking trash!
去死的他是不是说美金？
What the hell--
Is he talking dollars here?
不他在说谎
No, he's lying.
你骗我吗？
Did you fuck me?
你有没有骗我？
Did you fuck me on this?
当然没有爱迪！
Of course not, Edward!
那他在说什么？
Then what's he talking about?
他在说….
He's saying that...
朗骗我们
...Longdale fucked us...
这是绝对离谱的事
...which is so totally,
completely bizarre.
退后
Stay back.
离我远点
Stay away from me.
放下那把弓！
Put the bow down!
我告诉过你不要相信那龟蛋
I told you not to trust the prick.
朗先生如果变态佬
和色情行业之间
Mr. Longdale, if there's no honour...
没有道义存在的话
...among perverts and pornographers...
整个行业将会崩溃
..the whole business would fall apart.
因为我们没有记录没有合约
没有法律保障
Because there's no records,
no contracts, no legal recourse.
所以如果有人
So if someone...
欺骗我们
...cheats us...
那人不再被信任
...that person can't be trusted.
那人会把我们害死
That person could turn us in,
have us killed.
所以我们无选择余地
对吗朗先生
So we don't have a choice,
do we, Mr. Longdale?
我要这事完结
没有其他人要被伤害
I want this to be over.
Nobody else needs to get hurt.
爱迪把你的枪拿出来
Eddie, take your gun out.
操你
Fuck you.
拿出来放地上
Take it out now! And drop it.
不然我会开枪
Or I will shoot.
别那么傻爱迪
Don't be stupid, Edward.
用力踢过来
Kick it in my direction. Hard.
帝诺快放下那把弓
Now, Dino, drop the crossbow.
开始
Action.
错了
This is wrong.
搞错了
Something's wrong.
天啊不应是这样
God, not like this.
我应该有
I am supposed to have...
更多的电影感
...something more cinematic.
机器杀死他们
Kill them, Machine.
把他们全杀掉
Kill them all.
机器！
Machine!
不要动爱迪
Stop, Eddie!
我发誓
I swear to Christ!
我会向你背后开枪
I'll shoot you in the back!
除掉面具
Take off the mask.
除掉那他妈的面具！
Take off the fucking mask!
他只有一颗子弹
He's only got one bullet!
艾美小心听着
Amy, listen carefully.
-汤姆你在哪里？
-艾美听着
-Tom, where are you?
-Amy, just listen.
现在带仙蒂离开家
Take Cindy. Get out of the house now.
去我们渡国庆日周末的地方
Go to where we spent
Fourth of July weekend.
-为什么？出了什么岔？
-艾美我不能解释
-Why? What's wrong?
-Amy, please. l can't.
我三小时后会到
I'll be there in three hours.
我在途中快动身
I'm on my way! Go now!
汤姆你吓死我
Tom, you're scaring me.
艾美请你照我所说的去做
Please, Amy, just do it!
好再见我现在去
Okay, bye. I'm going.
克里斯太太这是汤威尔斯
Mrs. Christian, it's Tom Welles.
朗已死
Longdale is dead.
他被制作那套影片的人所杀
He was killed by the men
who made the film.
他为你丈夫雇用他们
但藏了一百万的大部份
He hired them for your husband.
Kept most of the million.
那影片是真的
The film is real!
他们杀死那少女
They killed that girl!
克里斯太太？
Mrs. Christian?
我仍在威尔斯先生
I'm still here, Mr. Welles.
对不起我知道这一定….
I'm sorry. I know this must be--
你有危险吗？
Are you in danger？.
我们要报警
我今晚将整件事告诉你
We'll go to the police.
I'll tell you everything tonight.
我们可以明早报警
We can call the police in the morning.
好的
All right.
八点整？
Eight o'clock?
八点整没有问题
Yes, eight o'clock is fine.
你知不知道….
Do you know...
那个可怜少女的名字
..what the poor girl's name was?
玛丽·安马修
Mary Anne Mathews.
谢谢你
Thank you.
再见威尔斯先生
Mr. Welles, goodbye.
你没事吗？
Are you okay?
Are you?
你为什么没有打电话给我？
Why haven't you called me?
你为什么在地球的表层失了踪
Why did you disappear
off the face of the Earth?
你在流血
You're bleeding.
这是手铐吗？
Are those handcuffs?
你被人锁起吗？
Were you locked up?
不准你打电话？发生什么事？
Kept from a phone? What happened?
汤姆说话呀
Start talking, Tom.
如果你不想离婚的话
你不能这样对我
Because if you want to stay married,
you can't treat me this way!
说得对
You're right.
你说的全部对
Everything you say is right.
汤姆这样不够
这样不能解决问题
That won't do it.
That's not enough, Tom.
不会
Not anymore.
我不会让任何事发生在我们身上
I'm not going to let
anything happen to us.
那你看我们现在
Look where we are!
看看你自己你看看你自己
Look at yourself!
Look at yourself! Look!
你这狗娘养的
You son of a bitch.
你根本不知道
你是让我怎么过的
You don't even have any idea
what you're putting me through.
我无法想像你发生什么事
What was I supposed to think
happened to you?
我们要在这里住几天
We're going to stay here a few days.
只是几天
It's just a few days.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
没有其他方法
There's no other way around this.
好了我发誓我发誓
Okay, look. I swear, I swear...
我不会让任何事发生在我们身上
我会处理
...I won't let anything happen to us.
I'll take care of it.
我发誓
I swear it.
我现在要出去
Now I have to go back out.
去哪里？
Where?
我要去见克里斯太太
I have to see Mrs. Christian.
她是唯一的证人
She's the only witness.
什么证人？
To what?
我们会没事的
We're going to be okay.
我是汤威尔斯我约了克里斯太太
Tom Welles.
Mrs. Christian's expecting me.
是她留下了指示
Yes, she left instructions.
我要立刻见她这是非常紧急
I have to see her now.
It's extremely urgent.
威尔斯先生克里斯太太在今天
下午结束了自己的生命
Mrs. Christian chose to take
her own life this afternoon, Mr. Welles.
但我刚….
But I just....
不不我刚….
No, no, I just....
我刚刚才跟她通过电话
I just spoke to her.
她留下了指示:第一个信封
Her instructions were
that this first envelope...
是给玛丽·安的家人
...is for Mary's family.
她写着你会明白什么意思
She wrote that you'd understand
what that meant.
第二个信封是给你的
And the second envelope is for you.
丧礼会在下星期举行
假如你想出席的话
Services will be held next week,
if you'd like to attend.
对不起先生
I am sorry, sir.
晚安先生
Good night, sir.
请忘记我们
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
我要回去
I have to go back.
不管什么事
Whatever it is...
不管你曾经去过哪里
...wherever you were...
把一切忘记
...just forget about it.
你留在此
You stay here.
我不能
I can't.
冒着我们的生命危险
冒着家人的危险？为什么？
And risk us? Risk your family? Why?
除了我没有人收拾残局
There's no one left
to finish this but me.
我会跟你说
什么时候可以安全回家
I'll call you when it's safe to go home.
当你回家时我们未必会在
We may not be there
when you get back.
仙蒂的教育还有其他的费用
Cindy's education, and a lot more.
我爱你
I love you.
跪下将手放在头上
Put your hands on your head.
Down on your knees.
你以为我是闹着玩？
You think I'm fucking around?
痛了吧？
Hurts, doesn't it?
你想他妈的怎样？
What the fuck do you want?
机器是谁？
Who's Machine?
他住在哪里？
Where does he live?
我不知道
I don't know.
我要他的名字
I want his name.
我不知道他的名字
I don't know his name.
伤害你我永远不会觉得累
I will never get tired of hurting you.
我不知道他的名字
他总是带着面具来带着面具走
I don't know his name. He shows up
in his mask, he leaves in his mask.
他住在纽约某区
He's from New York somewhere.
上车
Get in the car.
为什么？
Why?
我要你带我去你杀她的现场
You're going to show me
where you killed her.
操你
Fuck you.
好的他妈的
All right, you fuck.
你带她来之前对她做过什么？
What did you do before
you brought her here?
说她如何漂亮….
Tell her how beautiful she was...
你将会捧她成巨星
...how you'd make her a big star?
向她献殷勤？
Talk her up?
你想在我身上得到他妈的什么
What the fuck do you want from me?
我想知道
I want to know.
你想知道？
You want to know?
她不值一提
She was nothing.
流连在街上的小妓女
A little piece of pussy off the street.
像这样的少女失了踪
没人会理会
Girl like that disappears,
nobody gives a shit.
对我向她献殷勤
Yeah, I talked her up.
对她说她想听的话
对她说她会成为巨星
Told her everything she wanted to hear.
I told her she'd be a big star...
她会赚很多钱还有很多废话
...she'd make a lot of money,
and all the rest of the bullshit.
当我说完她已为那大荧幕试镜
感到异常兴奋
By the time I was finished, she was
all excited about her big screen test.
我打电话给帝诺
I called up Dino...
他和机器飞过来
我们开了一个小型派对
...he and Machine flew out here.
We had a little party.
你还想知道什么？
What else you want to know?
你看过那影片？
You saw the film, right?
你知道结局
You know the ending.
没有人看见你带她来这里？
Nobody else saw you bring her in?
谁会看见？这样的烂地方
Who's going to see?
Place is a fucking shithole.
我带她进来然后….
I brought her in and she...
她看见机器站在角落处
...saw Machine
standing in the corner.
她开始哭
She started crying...
发出些声音
...making these little noises.
我打了她要她安静
So I slapped her around a bit
just to shut her up.
帝诺….
Dino...
喂她吃了一些“药丸”
...fed her a bunch of pills.
机器在这里铺了几块胶布
Machine put down the plastic over here.
开始把她割开
Just started cutting her up.
就这样她死了
That's it. She's dead.
她死了那么久
除了你没有人会理会
She's been dead a long time.
Nobody gives a shit but you.
你想知道
You wanted to know.
现在你知道了
Now you know.
你当时在这里
You were in here.
你从这里看着玛丽·安流血至死
You watched Mary Anne
bleed to death from here.
为什么？
Why?
你为什么看？
Why did you watch?
我喜欢
I felt like it.
我从来没有看过人被杀
I never saw nobody get done before.
为什么？
Why?
你有兴奋你有射精吗？
Did you get hard? Did you come?
没有我感到作呕
No. It made me sick.
但这与我何干
But what do I give a shit...
假如一些富有疯子要对着这自渎
...if some rich fucking wacko wants
to beat off to something like that?
别起来！
Stay down!
我是为钱而做
It was something I did for money.
我需要那些他妈的钱
I needed the fucking money.
她在哪里？
Where is she?
你把她埋在哪里？
Where did you put her body?
我把它埋在丛林里
I buried it in the woods.
你不会找到
You're not going to find it.
就算你找到又如何？
你会得到什么？
If you find it, so what?
What do you got?
你只会得到一副骨骸
You got a girl's skeleton, that's it.
没有了影片你什么都没有
Without the film, you got nothing.
你可以做的是放我走
So all you can do is cut me loose.
因为没有了影片你什么都没有
Because without the film
you got nothing--
你他妈的在做什么？
What the fuck are you doing?!
-将手放在背后
-操你
-Put your hands behind your back.
-Fuck you!
将手放在背后
Put your hands behind your back!
好的
All right.
你他妈的在做什么？
What the fuck are you doing?
我准备杀了你
I'm going to kill you.
然后把你丢在这里
就像你对她一样
And I'm going to leave you here
just like you left her.
你不会杀我
You're not going to kill me.
你没有那种勇气
You don't have it in you.
你打算怎么做？用你的枪射我？
What are you going to do?
Shoot me with your own gun?
用你名字登记的枪
Registered in your name?
你小心地计划这行动是吗？
You really thought this through,
didn't you, genius?
你要将子弹从我的头挖出来
You'll have to dig
the bullets out of my head.
那会很有趣
That'll be nice.
或你可以掘一个洞
Or you could dig a hole.
用你的双手去掘
Dig it with your own hands...
然后将我埋在你的女朋友旁边
...and bury me next to your girlfriend.
动手吧
Go ahead.
开他妈的枪吧
Pull the fucking trigger.
动手吧
Go ahead.
你还在等什么？动手开枪吧
What are you waiting for?
Go ahead, do it.
你这同性恋
You faggot!
你要我做什么？哭？
What do you want me to do?
Start crying?
像婴儿般哭？
“我后悔杀了那少女”
Like a baby?
''I'm so sorry I killed the girl.''
操你！操她！
Fuck you! And fuck her!
动手吧带我脱离痛苦
开他妈的枪吧
Go ahead, put me out of my misery.
Pull the fucking trigger.
开他妈的枪吧
开吧
Do it!
你不敢开
You can't do it.
你这娘娘腔
You little pansy bitch!
你看你….
Look at you...
操你的大英雄
...big fucking hero, man.
你不敢开枪
You can't fucking do it.
看看他
Look at him.
他妈的大英雄
Big fucking hero.
快回到你太太那
Go on home to your wifey!
你这胆小鬼
You pussy!
你这他妈的胆小鬼
You big fucking pussy!
你现在可以做什么娘娘腔？
What are you going to do now, faggot?
你不能去报警
You can't go to the cops!
送你太太和女儿来
让我们制作一部影片你这娘娘腔
Send me your wife and daughter.
We'll make a film, you faggot!
操你
Shit.
你这无胆匪类
You punk-ass!
马修太太
Mrs. Mathews?
我是汤姆
It's Thomas.
汤贺特
Thomas Hart.
我几个星期前来问你女儿的事
I was there a few weeks ago
asking about your daughter.
嗯你找到她的日记
Yeah, you found her diary.
谢谢你
Thank you.
她有留字条
She did leave a note...
她的蠢男友在加州丢下她
...and her stupid boyfriend
dumped her in California...
我已经告诉了调查局
...so I told the FBI.
你是否记得….
Remember when...
我问过你想不想知道
...I asked you if you'd want to know...
事情的真相
...the truth...
无论是什么？
...no matter what?
几个男人捉了她
杀了她埋葬了她
Some men, they took her and
they killed her and they buried her.
不不
No, no.
我很难过
I'm sorry.
我要惩罚他们所做过的一切
I want to punish them for what they did.
你为什么告诉我这些？
Why are you saying this?
我可以伤害他们
I can hurt them.
请你准许我伤害他们
Give me your permission
to hurt them, please.
告诉我她对你有多大意义
Tell me how much she meant to you.
告诉我你爱她
Just tell me that you loved her.
请告诉我你爱她
Please tell me that you loved her.
我爱她
I love her.
我很爱她
I love her so much.
是谁？
Who's that?
不！
No!
去死我操你老母你去死
Die, you motherfucker, die!
纽约医院
New York Hospital.
请帮我转急诊室？
Can you connect me to the nurse?
急诊室
Emergency.
我是第十三分区的安德生巡佐
It's Lt. Anderson of the 13th precinct.
请问你们有没有收过一个
腹部受伤的成年男病人？
Have you admitted an adult male
with an abdominal wound...
四十八小时之内发生的
是刀伤意外
..in the last 48 hours?
A stabbing incident.
腹部受伤？
Abdominal wound?
没有一个也没有
No, not one.
谢谢
Thank you.
我在找一位被刀伤
约六呎的男人
I'm looking for a stabbing victim.
Male. Maybe six feet.
他提供了假的资料
Filed a bogus report.
好像星期一有一个
We had a guy in on Monday, l think.
应该是昨天或前天的事
lt would be yesterday
or the day before.
那对不起了
Sorry.
-皇后郡急诊室
-这是安德生巡佐
-Queens County Emergency.
-Hi, Lt. Anderson.
我们有个刀伤意外
We had a stabbing incident...
估计受害人提供一个假名给我们
...and supposed victim gave us
a false name.
是一个腹部受伤的男人
A male with an abdominal wound.
等等让我查一下记录
Hold on. Let me check my records.
昨天治疗过一位病人
There was a patient treated yesterday.
左手有星型纹身？
Star tattoo on his right hand?
对乔治希根
Yes. George Anthony Higgins.
医疗保险用了他妈妈
桃丽 丝希根的名字登记
lnsurance policy is under his
mother's name, Doris Veronica Higgins.
就是他请你将他的地址给我
That's him.
Can you give me an address?
也是用了他妈妈的地址登记
在达拉斯顿
It's under her address. Douglaston.
要街名吗？
Need a street?
我真的希望你今晚
可以陪我去教堂
l really wish you'd go
to church with me tonight.
我爱你儿子
l love you, son.
我十点前回来再见
I'll be home by 10. Bye-bye.
坚贞基督徒团契
You know the best part
of killing someone?
你知道杀人最精彩的部份
You know the best part
of killing someone?
是看着他们面上的表情
The look on their face.
那个表情….
It's that look...
不是当他们被吓唬
..not when they're threatened...
不是当你伤害他们
...not when you hurt them...
更不是当他们看见刀
...not even when they see the knife.
而是当他们感觉刀锋插入
It's when they feel the knife go in.
就是这
That's it.
那是惊讶
It's surprise.
他们不能相信这事真的发生
They can't believe
it's really happening.
她有这个表情
She had that look.
那少女….
The girl...
当她发觉那不光是小电影
...when she knew it wasn't just porno.
感觉我有多兴奋？
Feel how hard I am?
除下面具
Take off the mask.
你以为我会是一只怪物
What did you expect, a monster?
我叫乔治
My name's George.
你可能已经知道
Probably knew that already.
很难让你明白？
Can't get your mind around it?
我没有答案
I don't have any answers.
我所说的不会让你晚上睡得好
Nothing I say is going
to make you sleep easier at night.
我没有被毒打没有被性侵犯
I wasn't beaten. I wasn't molested.
妈妈没虐待我
Mommy didn't abuse me.
父亲没有强奸我
Daddy never raped me.
我就是我
I'm only what I am.
情形就是这样
That's all there is to it!
没有秘密
There's no mystery.
我所做的
我那样做是因为我喜欢
Things I do, I do them because
I like them.
因为我想做
Because I want to.
你被刀伤多少刀？
You've been stabbed? How many times?
先生请问你叫什么名字？
Sir, can you tell me your name?
是你吗？
Is that you?
我的天
My God.
救我
Save me.
谢谢
亲爱的威尔斯先生:
Dear Mr. Welles:
谢谢你的来信
Thank you for writing...
并告诉我你的真名字
...and telling me your real name...
你的真正身份和真正发生的事
...who you really are
and what really happened.
我很高兴那些人都死了
I'm glad those men are dead.
但我心灵的伤口却永远
不会被填平
But nothing will ever
fill the hole in my heart.
我会将你寄给我的钱做点好事
I will try to use
the money you sent for some good...
但会在我替自己疗伤之后
...after I get some help for myself.
我恨你将事实告诉我
I hated you
for telling me the truth...
但我感觉到你和我可能是
...but now I realize you and I
are probably the only people...
这世上唯一关心玛丽·安的人
...that ever really
cared about Mary Anne.
珍纳·马修
Yours truly...
敬上
...Janet Mathews.